The day started like every other. The earth rotated at 1,000 miles an hour. The sprinklers
clicked on at exactly 715. The paint on the garage peeled another 1.2 millimeters.
And Pete and I were hard at work meeting dad's high car wash standards. When suddenly...,...
voice! We need to talk. We didn't do it. Here's a quarter. Call my lawyer. Eddie's.
Pete. Pete. Every man dreams of a chance to say what I'm gonna say to you. A chance to see his
boys become men. To reach that apex. To climb. As usual we had no idea what dad was blamoring
on about. But then. I guess what I'm trying to say is your mother and I are going away for the
weekend. We're putting you in charge. The house. The doors. The doors. The doors. The doors.
no rules. accept one. beat your job is to protect the house and everything in it especially my most
precious possessions cherish them. love them. but under no circumstances I know I know. don't touch,
eat or play with anything that has one of those on. your charge. think you can handle a champ? in
my sleep. well that about covers it missing already. I believe there's just one more little detail.
they were more beautiful than I imagined. they were the keys to paradise. well,
we leave in you as boys. when you come back you'll be men. remember to change
your underwear. Joyce, let's go. you have to give them your compliments. your
faith. your trust. I can't do it now. my name is my name is called my precious life.
if you love something, set it free. remember
don. the tools are just a phone call
away. synchronize. 35 hours in counting.
this is it. just you and me. now begin.
it's so beautiful. it's like I've never
been here. it's so hours. I'm scared. I'm
here. three hours into our mega weekend.
I was already out of it. but not pee.
he was just warming up. rev it on the red line. the reglie 500 is about
to begin. it was time for the main event. the reglie 500. a gut crunching
500 lap race around the house. up till that weekend. it had only been a
dream. but with mom and dad gone nothing could stop us. well, almost nothing.
okay. her name was Margie Corso. I had written it a thousand times on my math notebook. and here she was
in my front yard. what are you guys doing? we were just to clean it up. cleaning? there's no cleaning.
and there will be no cleaning. we're gonna want the reglie 500. it's okay. I was just seeing if you
wanted to come swimming with me at the quarry. sorry. but brother and I are busy for the next 32 hours.
it's the age of Pete. right? right? it's no big deal. I understand if you're out of
play with your little brother. it would be the ultimate betrayal. but this was Margie.
she'd a way of tugging her earlobes. did kill with me. it's just a race. we can ride
bikes anytime. you don't mind, do you? I'll tell you what. while I'm gone. the whole house
is yours. you're in charge. as that sound. neat, huh? you think you can handle it, champ?
I guess I thought that Pete would understand that I'd been trying to get a date with
Margie since last summer. think again, Johnny. so I said to him, dad. buddy. it's like this.
you scratch my back. I'll scratch yours. wow. the whole house yourself. this morning? I
started with a refrigerator door open for 45
minutes. just because I could. always wanted
to do that. you want to come in for some
milk? we can drink straight from the carton.
excuse me sir, can I help you?
no. I live here. that was a funny one.
now it's my turn. knock knock. who's
there? not you? the house has been sold.
sold? what do you mean? sold. the buyer in the seller reached an equitable agreement in which
the seller waves escrow rights exchange for cash though. huh? let me explain it to you. you don't
live here anymore. your brother sold the house. you got it? it's not brain surgery. I should
know. I used to be a brain surgeon until they fired me. you leave a sandwich inside of one head.
my card. Margie, can you give me a second here? I gotta talk to my brother.
you want to come in? no. maybe you two should work this out. besides.
milk makes me off learning. we've got water. short pea. we'll spend a
whole weekend together. how could you do this? easy. they met my price.
have you lost it? dad's gonna kill us. no? i'm just gonna kill you. you're gonna charge. what's
the liar with you? you grow up? you grow up? good. i feel like a baby now. boys, like i always
say. fighting is no way to solve your problems. Roy Kretchmar, and this here is the Mrs and the
two sprouts. where the new owners of your lovely house. how do you like to come in for some book?
I'm sorry. You see, there's
been some sort of mistake.
My brother's right. I
got to give you these.
You're bathroom comes equipped with
matching brass fixtures and deluxe fully
operational toilets.
The plumbing shot.
Don't expect to go number
two in either of them.
That won't be a problem.
And here's a place to escape the ups and
downs of the day. Your own secret hideaway.
There's nails poking
down from the ceiling.
But you know, it's roomier
than it looks from the outside.
Oh, our first phone call.
Cretch my residence.
Don't worry. We're just
a phone call in the way.
Cretch my residence.
Hello? Hi, honey.
I'm glad I got you.
How's everything?
Uh, pretty much the same.
Well, don't go selling the
house or anything crazy like that.
Right. Sell the house. Funny.
How'd it go?
Your father's gassed himself again.
How'd call you later? Later.
When? Mom? Like a dog
with a bladder problem.
The Cretchmores were
leaving their mark everywhere.
There was no way around
it. I had let my dad down.
And if I didn't
stop this insanity,
he was gonna stop me from living.
You're in charge. That's what my dad said.
He trusted me with his whole house.
And now I trusted him to take my head off
with a nine iron. What else could go wrong?
How about a garage sale of
all my family's possessions?
What's going on?
Well, like I always say, one man's
trash is another man's treasure.
But this is our treasure.
I mean, if you're gonna
get rid of all our stuff, why don't you just
have your duty to leave back for a buck?
Sold! Thanks Mr.
Cretchmara. There's so much
nicer than the death use to live here.
But that's my dad. He'll kill you.
You see?
Peter bought you this for your birthday.
What's it doing on the damaged goods table?
Well, it is missing an eye,
but it's yours for 15 cents.
Sold! The Cretchmars were
as unstoppable as a lava flow.
If I was gonna get the
house and all our junk back,
I was gonna have to call in the troops.
Count me in.
The Cretchmars have the nicest neighbors on
the block. Why would I want them to leave?
Because if they stay, my family'll
have to leave the neighborhood.
And that means Peter
will be gone forever.
They'll be sad and alone
the rest of your miserable life.
Okay, count me in.
Holy moly. Not bad for a buck.
Howdy partner! I'm known as F.
McNamara.
That stands for free range.
I know if they told you this.
But your house is on the
official Wellsville catalog.
Nearly full day a step aside, I'll get this
little dog into a lazy garage by something.
Come right in. Like my royal way says.
When you've got fresh cookies,
you can't go wrong with fresh milk.
Help yourself partner.
Come on.
Man, I'm from the fight
the airport committee.
Are you aware that you live under one
of the nation's busiest flight patterns?
And that some airports have shot
at guidelines for luggage control.
Lovely. Like my royal way says,
you can't go wrong with free clothes.
And Billy just loves airplanes.
He's in junior pilot school.
I'll get it.
Pete, just calling to remind you
there's a casserole in the fridge.
Yeah, we found it.
And don't forget, we'll be
home tomorrow at 7 o'clock.
No rush.
The clock was ticking.
In 21 hours, I beat grilled Pete.
I had to get the crutchmores
out, and I had to find a pro.
Into a riggly. All these years I've
known you never treat me as a friend.
Never. And find me in your
house for a cool beverage.
Are you filming? Thanks Mike.
Oh, the boy's the shopper
never going to believe this, huh?
A desperate carrot that
comes to me for hell.
Beautiful.
Say we get down to
business, shall we? I help you.
What's in front
of you? Anything.
You can break everything
in the house, dig up the yard,
contaminated with nuclear waste.
You got any, uh, knee-paulton ice cream.
Good riggly.
Welcome! My nightmare.
That night, I expected to find the
crutchmars running for their lives,
and endless Mike standing
atop a pile of furniture
laughing his flames
burst all around him.
Instead.
Man, those crutchmars can't fart.
I don't believe you.
Do you realize this is our last night here?
Mom and Dad trusted us to be
responsible, and now look at us.
It's your fault. I know.
I put you in charge.
I thought you'd have grown up for once.
Oh, so acting grown up
means ditching your brother on
the one most ultimate weekend
we could have ever had.
You're still thinking about that
stupid weekend. Don't you get it?
When mom and dad get back,
we're gonna be grounded for life.
They can't ground us.
We don't have a house.
That's it. I've had enough.
I'm out of here.
One.
What do you think you're doing?
Well, you promised you
yesterday, traitor, the really 500.
Have you lost it?
Mom and Dad are practically on their way
home and you want to ride bikes? Life short.
Live large.
I'm a lap ahead of you.
What are you gonna do about it?
I don't know why I cared,
but if I couldn't get our
house back, the next best
thing was with Pete's butt.
I'm gonna crush you like road kill.
You're gun soil loujec.
Put your nuts, slow head.
I'm not sure when it happened.
Could have been the inside turn on lap 325.
But closing in on Pete, I realized
I was actually having a great time.
And I knew why. For me, there's never
been a better friend than my own brother.
Sure, the race ended in a tie, but I
wouldn't have had it any other way.
Nice race.
Yeah, nice race.
I'm sorry, Pete.
I'm sorry I did shit. Never again.
Yeah, well, I'm sorry I sold her a house.
This weekend to do our Riggly 500.
Before dad this owns me.
You won't have to. We still got...
Four minutes?
And a problem is?
Huh? Don't worry. I have plenty.
Oh!
Oh! Isn't this a surprise?
Can we talk to you and Mr.
Cretchmar? Like now?
Well, certainly.
Oh, Roy!
What can I do for you, fellas?
This is your eviction notice, Roy.
Either you go or the house goes.
Well, I can see you mean business.
Good vision.
You have 10 seconds.
Whoa! Let's not be hasty.
Like I always say.
You don't live here anymore.
With time running out and mom and
dad in sight, there was one option left.
Please, please, please.
But this is our home.
Our lives are in these walls.
Like right here, these
notches are repeating.
I would measure ourselves growing up.
And look, these footprints,
they repeat first steps.
We've spent our whole lives in this house.
It's where Pete and I first met.
Please.
I think I understand.
This house really means a lot to you.
So you sell it back to us? Well.
No! We'll build on the memories.
Oh, Pete, it's a nice milling here.
You've been a good brother.
Now it's the age of Pete.
Hey, daddy!
Congratulations, sons.
Hey, you're wrinkly.
No, no, you're more than wrinkly.
You're men.
Breathe, honest, manly.
Mommy!
Oh, well, what a lovely welcome.
Oh, and who are these nice people?
Say hello to the Kretchmars.
It's so nice to meet you.
You've kept a lovely home.
Oh, so you folks live around here?
You could say that?
Right here, in fact.
Got quite a deal, too.
I don't follow you, stranger.
We kind of sold them the house.
Oh, huh.
After dad calmed down a bed,
he looked at our side of things,
and got even madder.
But a week later,
Mr. Kretchmars was transferred
to Alaska, and we
got our house back.
As for Pete and I, we
agreed to spend the
whole weekend together
the next time we get the
us to ourselves, which knowing
mom and dad will be in about 30 years.