( Upbeat trumpet playing )
BIG PETE:
The day started like every other.
The Earth rotated
at 1,000 miles an hour,
the sprinklers clicked on
at exactly 7:15,
the paint on the garage peeled
another 1.2 millimeters,
and Pete and I were hard at work
meeting Dad's high car wash standards,
when suddenly...
Boys, we need to talk.
Uh we didn't do it.
Here's a quarter, call my lawyer.
At ease.
Pete. Pete.
Every man dreams of a chance to say
what I'm gonna say to you.
A chance to see his boys
become men.
To reach that apex.
To climb... ( fading into background )
BIG PETE:
As usual, we had no idea
what dad was blammering on about.
But, then...
I guess what I'm trying to say is,
you're mother and I
are going away for the weekend.
We're putting you in charge.
The house is yours.
( "is yours" continues echoing )
( Trumpets crescendo )
{\
Title Sequence
}